[
  {
    "question": "Inside which HTML element do we put the JavaScript??1",
    "choice1": "<script>",
    "choice2": "<javascript>",
    "choice3": "<js>",
    "choice4": "<scripting>",
    "answer" : 1
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the correct syntax for referring to an external script called 'xxx.js'?2",
    "choice1": "<script href='xxx.js'>",
    "choice2": "<script name='xxx.js'>",
    "choice3": "<script src='xxx.js'>",
    "choice4": "<script file='xxx.js'>",
    "answer" : 3
  },
  {
    "question": " How do you write 'Hello World' in an alert box?3",
    "choice1": "msgBox('Hello World');",
    "choice2": "alertBox('Hello World');",
    "choice3": "msg('Hello World');",
    "choice4": "alert('Hello World');",
    "answer" : 4
  },
  {
    "question": "Inside which HTML element do we put the JavaScript??4",
    "choice1": "<script>",
    "choice2": "<javascript>",
    "choice3": "<js>",
    "choice4": "<scripting>",
    "answer" : 1
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the correct syntax for referring to an external script called 'xxx.js'?5",
    "choice1": "<script href='xxx.js'>",
    "choice2": "<script name='xxx.js'>",
    "choice3": "<script src='xxx.js'>",
    "choice4": "<script file='xxx.js'>",
    "answer" : 3
  },
  {
    "question": " How do you write 'Hello World' in an alert box?6",
    "choice1": "msgBox('Hello World');",
    "choice2": "alertBox('Hello World');",
    "choice3": "msg('Hello World');",
    "choice4": "alert('Hello World');",
    "answer" : 4
  },
  {
    "question": "Inside which HTML element do we put the JavaScript??7",
    "choice1": "<script>",
    "choice2": "<javascript>",
    "choice3": "<js>",
    "choice4": "<scripting>",
    "answer" : 1
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the correct syntax for referring to an external script called 'xxx.js'?8",
    "choice1": "<script href='xxx.js'>",
    "choice2": "<script name='xxx.js'>",
    "choice3": "<script src='xxx.js'>",
    "choice4": "<script file='xxx.js'>",
    "answer" : 3
  },
  {
    "question": " How do you write 'Hello World' in an alert box?9",
    "choice1": "msgBox('Hello World');",
    "choice2": "alertBox('Hello World');",
    "choice3": "msg('Hello World');",
    "choice4": "alert('Hello World');",
    "answer" : 4
  },
  {
    "question": " How do you write 'Hello World' in an alert box?10",
    "choice1": "msgBox('Hello World');",
    "choice2": "alertBox('Hello World');",
    "choice3": "msg('Hello World');",
    "choice4": "alert('Hello World');",
    "answer" : 4
  }
]